<resources>
    // Fragments
    <string name="app_name">Murder &amp; Mysteries</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="characters">Characters</string>
    <string name="invitation">Invitation</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="mysteries">Mysteries</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">How to Play</string>
    <string name="awards">Awards</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="new_party">New Party</string>
    <string name="evidence">Evidence</string>
    <string name="accusation">Accusation &amp; Awards</string>

    // Mysteries Fragment
    <string name="mystery_players">%1$d - %2$d</string>
    <string name="buy_mystery">Buy Mystery</string>
    <string name="host_party">Host Party</string>

    // How to play Fragment
    <string name="how_to_play_title">How to Play</string>
    <string name="invitation_icon">Invitation icon</string>
    <string name="plan_your_party">1. Plan your party</string>
    <string name="calendar_icon">Calendar icon</string>
    <string name="instructions_1_body">You choose a theme for your mystery, and decide on a night to host your party.</string>
    <string name="instructions_2_title">2. Send invitations</string>
    <string name="instructions_2_body">Invite your guests to install the app. You\'ll assign them a character, or let them choose their own.</string>
    <string name="party_icon">Party icon</string>
    <string name="instructions_3_title">3. Mystery night</string>
    <string name="instructions_3_body">Your guests will arrive in character, and everyone will receive information and objectives.</string>
    <string name="murder_icon">Murder icon</string>
    <string name="instructions_4_title">4. Murder</string>
    <string name="instructions_4_body">After everyone has had time to eat, drink and mingle, someone will be informed that they are the victim and another guest, the murderer.</string>
    <string name="magnifying_glass_icon">Magnifying glass icon</string>
    <string name="instructions_5_title">5. Solve the mystery</string>
    <string name="instructions_5_body">Everyone will be presented with clues about the murder. You will attempt to use these clues, and the information you glean from others, to solve the mystery.</string>
    <string name="trophy_icon">Trophy icon</string>
    <string name="instructions_6_title">6. Accusations</string>
    <string name="instructions_6_body">At the end of the night everyone will accuse someone of committing the murder. Prizes will be given out to those who guessed right, and other categories like best dressed and best actor.</string>
    <string name="awards_description">Awards you earned from previous mystery parties will be shown here.</string>
    <string name="having_problems">Having problems?</string>
    <string name="report_an_issue">Report an issue</string>
    <string name="love_this_app">Love this app?</string>
    <string name="leave_a_rating">Leave a rating</string>

    // Invitation Fragment
    <string name="youre_invited">You\'re invited</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_invite_body_1"><b>► As host, the first thing to do is invite people to your party.</b> You\'re guests will receive a link to download the app and view their invitation.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_invite_body_2"><b>► Ask your guests to review the mystery before your party.</b> You\'re guests will be able to read their invitation, the Guest Guide instructions and the Feast Announcement.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_invite_body_3"><b>► This app facilitates the game and makes hosting easy.</b> The app is an essential component for all players. If for some reason someone cannot bring their device for your party, ask someone if they have an extra loaner device.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_characters_body_1"><b>► Before your party, you will need to assign a character to each guest from the Characters screen.</b> Your guest will be notified that they\'ve been assigned a character and they will be able to read their character\'s backstory.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_characters_body_2"><b>► Neither you nor your guests will know whether they are victim or murderer before the party.</b> This makes the reveal a surprise and allows for better role playing and deduction.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_characters_body_3"><b>► You and your guests can read a short description of each character.</b> When you assign characters, try to match your guests to a character. Certain characters will be a part of a couple or related to other characters.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_1"><b>► When your party is scheduled to start, the app will begin Stage 1: Arrival.</b> All players will be able to see their first objectives, things their character\'s know and their inventory.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_2"><b>► Allow time for guests to arrive.</b> Everyone can mingle in character, and get introduced to each other. Once everyone has arrived, you (the host) will have the option on the Party screen to begin Stage 2: Welcome.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_3"><b>► Elowynn Lockwood will receive a script to read to welcome all to the feast.</b> Give the guests 30 \- 60 minutes to mingle and complete their first objectives. When you are ready, you can proceed the party to Stage 3: Murder.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_4"><b>► The victim will receive a notification.</b> They will let you know they are ready for the murder.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_5"><b>► The countess will receive a notification.</b> The countess will be instructed to wait for you to tell them when to make their toast.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_6"><b>► When the countess makes their toast and everyone takes a drink, the victim will fall over dead.</b> The captain of the city guard will read a script to start the murder investigation.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_7"><b>► Everyone will now have their second set of objectives and information.</b> Give the players time to complete their second objectives and discuss the murder. Once the captain has collected all evidence proceed to Stage 4: Evidence.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_8"><b>► Captain Jarin will present their findings to the guests.</b> Everyone will be able to see the evidence on their devices. Give them time to review the evidence, and make their accusations using the app.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_9"><b>► Once everyone has made an accusation, and voted for best dressed and best acting, you will receive a notification.</b> You can now proceed to Stage 5: Solution.</string>
    <string name="instructions_host_timeline_body_10"><b>► Captain Jerin will read the solution aloud to everyone.</b> Awards will be handed out via the app and everyone will be able to see the winners.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="players_icon">Players icon</string>
    <string name="my_character">My Character</string>
    <string name="objectives">Objectives</string>
    <string name="inventory">Inventory</string>

</resources>
